Wyck Association Collection 1663-1972 Mss.Ms.Coll.52
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Financial materials, 1746-1972; 33.25 Linear feet 80 boxes
  - A. Accounts
    - OVERSIZED accounts
      - Account Books
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I, Account Book, 1858-1887 (Box PB7, Folder 176)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1859-1863 (Box PB7, Folder 177)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book "Heidelberg Farm Accounts", 1871-1916 (Box PB7, Folder 178)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1880-1884 (Box PB7, Folder 179)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1884-1887 (Box PB7, Folder 180)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1887-1889 (Box PB7, Folder 181)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1890-1891 (Box PB7, Folder 182)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book, 1891-1893 (Box PB7, Folder 183)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book "Farm Inventory", 1895 (Box PB7, Folder 184)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book "Heidelberg Farm Accounts", 1917-1929 (Box PB7, Folder 185)
        - Haines, Robert Bowne I Account Book "Lists of stock", 1929-1937 (Box PB7, Folder 186)
  - B. Bills and Receipts
    - Reuben Haines I
      - 1762-1766 (Box 145, Folder 183)
      - 1767-1771 (Box 145, Folder 184)
      - 1772 (Box 145, Folder 185)
      - 1773 (Box 145, Folder 186)
      - 1774 (Box 145, Folder 187)
      - 1775 (Box 145, Folder 188)
      - 1776-1777 (Box 145, Folder 189)
      - 1778-1783 (Box 145, Folder 190)
      - 1784-1785 (Box 145, Folder 191)
      - 1785-1787 (Box 145, Folder 192)
      - 1786 (Box 145, Folder 193)
      - 1787-1788 (Box 145, Folder 194)
      - 1789-1790 (Box 145, Folder 195)
      - 1791-1793 (Box 145, Folder 196)
      - n.d. (Box 145, Folder 197)
    - Margaret Wistar Haines
      - 1759 (Box 145, Folder 197a)
    - Richard Hartshorne
      - 1803, 1811-1814 (Box 145, Folder 198)
      - 1815-1817 (Box 145, Folder 199)
      - 1819-1820 (Box 145, Folder 200)
    - Caspar Wistar Haines I
      - 1785-1794 (Box 145, Folder 201)
      - 1795-1797 (Box 145, Folder 202)
      - 1798-1801 (Box 145, Folder 203)
      - n.d. (Box 145, Folder 204)
    - Josiah Haines
      - 1789-1791 (Box 145, Folder 205)
      - 1795 (Box 145, Folder 206)
    - Reuben Haines II
      - 1790 (Box 145, Folder 207)
    - Reuben Haines III
      - 1800-1808 (Box 146, Folder 208)
      - 1809 (Box 146, Folder 209)
      - 1810-1812 (Box 146, Folder 210)
      - 1813-1814 (Box 146, Folder 211)
      - 1815, 1816 (Box 146, Folder 212)
      - 1817-1819 (Box 146, Folder 213)
      - 1820 (Box 146, Folder 214)
      - 1822 (Box 146, Folder 215)
      - 1824, 1826 (Box 146, Folder 216)
      - 1827-1836 (Box 146, Folder 217)
      - n.d. (Box 146, Folder 218)
    - Jane Bowne Haines I
      - 1832-1835 (Box 146, Folder 219)
      - 1837-1840 (Box 146, Folder 220)
      - 1841 (Box 146, Folder 221)
      - 1842 (Box 146, Folder 222)
      - 1843 (Box 146, Folder 223)
      - n.d. (Box 146, Folder 224)
    - Ann Haines
      - 1811-1861 (Box 146, Folder 225)
      - 1862-1863 (Box 146, Folder 226)
      - 1864-1865 (Box 146, Folder 227)
      - 1866-1867 (Box 146, Folder 228)
      - 1868-1869 (Box 146, Folder 229)
    - William Henry Bacon
      - 1852-1868 (Box 146, Folder 230)
    - John Smith Haines II
      - 1839-1842 (Box 146, Folder 231)
      - 1843 (Box 146, Folder 232)
      - 1844-1845 (Box 146, Folder 233)
      - 1846-1849 (Box 146, Folder 234)
      - 1850-1863 (Box 146, Folder 235)
      - 1880-1883 (Box 146, Folder 236)
      - 1884-1886 (Box 146, Folder 237)
      - 1891-1892 (Box 146, Folder 238)
    - Robert Bowne Haines I
      - 1848-1873 (Box 147, Folder 239)
      - 1852-1857 (Box 147, Folder 240)
      - n.d. (Box 147, Folder 241)
    - Margaret Vaux Wistar Haines
      - 1869-1891 (Box 147, Folder 242)
      - 1895-1900 (Box 147, Folder 243)
      - 1903-1919 (Box 147, Folder 244)
      - 1931-1935 (Box 147, Folder 245)
    - Jane Reuben Haines
      - 1875-1885 (Box 147, Folder 246)
      - 1886 (Box 147, Folder 247)
      - 1887-1890 (Box 147, Folder 248)
      - 1891-1892 (Box 147, Folder 249)
      - 1893-1899 (Box 147, Folder 250)
      - 1901-1904 (Box 147, Folder 251)
      - 1905 (Box 147, Folder 252)
      - 1906 (Box 147, Folder 253)
      - 1906 (Box 147, Folder 254)
      - 1907 (Box 147, Folder 255)
      - 1908-1909 (Box 147, Folder 256)
      - 1910 (Box 147, Folder 257)
      - 1911 (Box 147, Folder 258)
      - 1911 (Box 147, Folder 259)
      - 1911 (Box 147, Folder 260)
      - 1911 (Box 147, Folder 261)
    - Caspar Wistar Haines II
      - 1870-1874 (Box 147, Folder 262)
      - 1875-1877 (Box 147, Folder 263)
      - 1878 (Box 147, Folder 264)
      - 1879-1880 (Box 147, Folder 265)
      - 1881-1884 (Box 147, Folder 266)
      - 1888 (Box 147, Folder 267)
      - 1891-1892 (Box 147, Folder 268)
      - 1892-1895 (Box 148, Folder 269)
      - 1896-1899 (Box 148, Folder 270)
      - 1900-1905 (Box 148, Folder 271)
      - 1906-1909 (Box 148, Folder 272)
      - 1910 (Box 148, Folder 273)
      - 1911 (Box 148, Folder 274)
      - 1912 (Box 148, Folder 275)
      - 1912 (Box 148, Folder 276)
      - 1912 (Box 148, Folder 277)
      - 1912 (Box 148, Folder 278)
      - 1913 (Box 148, Folder 279)
      - 1913 (Box 148, Folder 280)
      - 1913 (Box 148, Folder 281)
      - 1913 (Box 148, Folder 282)
      - 1914 (Box 148, Folder 283)
      - 1914 (Box 148, Folder 284)
      - 1914 (Box 148, Folder 285)
      - 1915 (Box 148, Folder 286)
      - 1915 (Box 148, Folder 287)
      - 1915 (Box 148, Folder 288)
      - 1915 (Box 148, Folder 289)
      - 1916 (Box 148, Folder 290)
      - 1916 (Box 148, Folder 291)
      - 1916 (Box 148, Folder 292)
      - 1916 (Box 148, Folder 293)
      - 1917 (Box 148, Folder 294)
      - 1917 (Box 148, Folder 295)
      - 1917 (Box 148, Folder 296)
      - 1917 (Box 148, Folder 297)
      - 1918 (Box 149, Folder 298)
      - 1918 (Box 149, Folder 299)
      - 1918 (Box 149, Folder 300)
      - 1918 (Box 149, Folder 301)
      - 1918 (Box 149, Folder 302)
      - 1919 (Box 149, Folder 303)
      - 1919 (Box 149, Folder 304)
      - 1919 (Box 149, Folder 305)
      - 1919 (Box 149, Folder 306)
      - 1919 (Box 149, Folder 307)
      - 1920 (Box 149, Folder 308)
      - 1920 (Box 149, Folder 309)
      - 1920 (Box 149, Folder 310)
      - 1920 (Box 149, Folder 311)
      - 1932 (Box 149, Folder 312)
      - 1921 (Box 149, Folder 313)
      - 1921 (Box 149, Folder 314)
      - 1921 (Box 149, Folder 315)
      - 1922 (Box 149, Folder 316)
      - 1922 (Box 149, Folder 317)
      - 1922 (Box 149, Folder 318)
      - 1922 (Box 149, Folder 319)
      - 1923 (Box 149, Folder 320)
      - 1923 (Box 149, Folder 321)
      - 1923 (Box 149, Folder 322)
      - 1923 (Box 149, Folder 323)
      - 1924 (Box 150, Folder 324)
      - 1924 (Box 150, Folder 325)
      - 1924 (Box 150, Folder 326)
      - 1924 (Box 150, Folder 327)
      - 1925 (Box 150, Folder 328)
      - 1925 (Box 150, Folder 329)
      - 1925 (Box 150, Folder 330)
      - 1925 (Box 150, Folder 331)
      - 1926 (Box 150, Folder 332)
      - 1926 (Box 150, Folder 333)
      - 1926 (Box 150, Folder 334)
      - 1927 (Box 150, Folder 335)
      - 1927 (Box 150, Folder 336)
      - 1927 (Box 150, Folder 337)
      - 1928 (Box 150, Folder 338)
      - 1928 (Box 150, Folder 339)
      - 1928 (Box 150, Folder 340)
      - 1929 (Box 150, Folder 341)
      - 1929 (Box 150, Folder 342)
      - 1929 (Box 150, Folder 343)
      - 1929 (Box 150, Folder 344)
      - 1930 (Box 150, Folder 345)
      - 1930 (Box 150, Folder 346)
      - 1930 (Box 150, Folder 347)
      - 1930 (Box 150, Folder 348)
      - 1931 (Box 150, Folder 349)
      - 1931 (Box 150, Folder 350)
      - 1931 (Box 151, Folder 351)
      - 1932 (Box 151, Folder 352)
      - 1932 (Box 151, Folder 353)
      - 1932 (Box 151, Folder 354)
      - 1933 (Box 151, Folder 355)
      - 1933 (Box 151, Folder 356)
      - 1933 (Box 151, Folder 357)
      - 1934 (Box 151, Folder 358)
      - 1934 (Box 151, Folder 359)
      - 1934 (Box 151, Folder 360)
      - 1934 (Box 151, Folder 361)
      - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 362)
      - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 363)
      - 1935 (Box 151, Folder 364)
      - 1936-1938 (Box 151, Folder 365)
      - 1919-1936 (Box 151, Folder 366)
      - n.d. (Box 151, Folder 367)
    - Caspar Wistar Haines II, Jane Bowne Haines II, and Mary Morton Haines
      - 1914-1918 (Box 151, Folder 368)
      - 1919-1930 (Box 151, Folder 369)
    - Robert Bowne Haines II
      - 1874, 1888-1891 (Box 151, Folder 370)
      - 1892 (Box 151, Folder 371)
      - 1893 (Box 151, Folder 372)
      - 1893 (Box 151, Folder 373)
      - 1894 (Box 151, Folder 374)
      - 1896-1896 (Box 151, Folder 375)
      - 1897 (Box 262, Folder 376)
      - 1898 (Box 151, Folder 377)
      - 1899 (Box 151, Folder 378)
      - 1900 (Box 152, Folder 379)
      - 1900 (Box 152, Folder 380)
      - 1901 (Box 152, Folder 381)
      - 1901 (Box 152, Folder 382)
      - 1901 (Box 152, Folder 383)
      - 1902 (Box 152, Folder 384)
      - 1902 (Box 152, Folder 385)
      - 1902 (Box 152, Folder 386)
      - 1903 (Box 152, Folder 387)
      - 1903 (Box 152, Folder 388)
      - 1903 (Box 152, Folder 389)
      - 1904 (Box 152, Folder 390)
      - 1904 (Box 152, Folder 391)
      - 1904 (Box 152, Folder 392)
      - 1905 (Box 152, Folder 393)
      - 1905 (Box 152, Folder 394)
      - 1905 (Box 152, Folder 395)
      - 1906 (Box 152, Folder 396)
      - 1906 (Box 152, Folder 397)
      - 1906 (Box 152, Folder 398)
      - 1907 (Box 152, Folder 399)
      - 1907 (Box 152, Folder 400)
      - 1907 (Box 152, Folder 401)
      - 1908 (Box 153, Folder 402)
      - 1908 (Box 153, Folder 403)
      - 1908 (Box 153, Folder 404)
      - 1909 (Box 153, Folder 405)
      - 1910 (Box 153, Folder 406)
      - 1911 (Box 153, Folder 407)
      - 1911 (Box 153, Folder 408)
      - 1912-1913 (Box 153, Folder 409)
      - 1914 (Box 153, Folder 410)
      - 1915 (Box 153, Folder 411)
      - 1916 (Box 153, Folder 412)
      - 1917-1918 (Box 153, Folder 413)
      - 1919 (Box 153, Folder 414)
      - 1920 (Box 153, Folder 415)
      - 1920 (Box 153, Folder 416)
      - 1921-1922 (Box 153, Folder 417)
      - 1923 (Box 153, Folder 418)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 153, Folder 419)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 153, Folder 420)
      - 1928-1929 (Box 153, Folder 421)
      - 1930 (Box 153, Folder 422)
      - 1930 (Box 153, Folder 423)
      - 1931 (Box 153, Folder 424)
      - 1931 (Box 154, Folder 425)
      - 1932 (Box 154, Folder 426)
      - n.d. (Box 154, Folder 427)
    - Mary Morton Haines
      - 1910-1913 (Box 154, Folder 428)
      - 1914-1917 (Box 154, Folder 429)
      - 1918-1919 (Box 154, Folder 430)
      - 1920 (Box 154, Folder 431)
      - 1921 (Box 154, Folder 432)
      - 1922 (Box 154, Folder 433)
      - 1923 (Box 154, Folder 434)
      - 1924 (Box 154, Folder 435)
      - 1925 (Box 154, Folder 436)
      - 1926 (Box 154, Folder 437)
      - 1927 (Box 154, Folder 438)
      - 1928 (Box 154, Folder 439)
      - 1931-1946 (Box 154, Folder 440)
      - n.d. (Box 154, Folder 441)
    - William Jones Haines
      - 1888-1914 (Box 154, Folder 442)
      - 1915-1916 (Box 154, Folder 443)
      - 1917 (Box 154, Folder 444)
      - 1917 (Box 154, Folder 445)
      - 1917 (Box 154, Folder 446)
      - 1917, 1934 (Box 154, Folder 447)
    - Jane Bowne Haines II
      - 1900-1910 (Box 154, Folder 448)
      - 1910 (Box 154, Folder 449)
      - 1910 (Box 154, Folder 450)
      - 1910 (Box 154, Folder 451)
      - 1911 (Box 155, Folder 452)
      - 1911 (Box 155, Folder 453)
      - 1911 (Box 155, Folder 454)
      - 1911 (Box 155, Folder 455)
      - 1912 (Box 155, Folder 456)
      - 1912 (Box 155, Folder 457)
      - 1912 (Box 155, Folder 458)
      - 1912 (Box 155, Folder 459)
      - 1913 (Box 155, Folder 460)
      - 1916-1929 (Box 155, Folder 461)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 155, Folder 462)
      - 1932 (Box 155, Folder 463)
      - 1932 (Box 155, Folder 464)
      - 1933 (Box 155, Folder 465)
      - 1933 (Box 155, Folder 466)
      - 1934 (Box 155, Folder 467)
      - 1934 (Box 155, Folder 468)
      - 1935 (Box 155, Folder 469)
      - 1935 (Box 156, Folder 470)
      - 1936-1941 (Box 156, Folder 471)
      - n.d. (Box 156, Folder 472)
    - Janes Bowne Haines II and Mary Morton Haines
      - 1910-1935 (Box 156, Folder 473)
    - Robert Bowne Haines III
      - 1920-1922 (Box 156, Folder 474)
      - 1923-1927 (Box 156, Folder 475)
      - 1928-1929 (Box 156, Folder 476)
      - 1930 (Box 156, Folder 477)
      - 1931-1934 (Box 156, Folder 478)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 156, Folder 479)
      - 1937 (Box 156, Folder 480)
      - 1938 (Box 156, Folder 481)
      - 1938 (Box 156, Folder 482)
      - 1939 (Box 156, Folder 483)
      - 1940 (Box 156, Folder 484)
      - 1940 (Box 156, Folder 485)
      - 1940 (Box 156, Folder 486)
      - 1940 (Box 156, Folder 487)
      - 1941 (Box 156, Folder 488)
      - 1941 (Box 157, Folder 489)
      - 1941 (Box 157, Folder 490)
      - 1941 (Box 157, Folder 491)
      - 1941 (Box 157, Folder 492)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 493)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 494)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 495)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 496)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 497)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 498)
      - 1942 (Box 157, Folder 499)
      - 1943 (Box 157, Folder 500)
      - 1943 (Box 158, Folder 501)
      - 1944 (Box 158, Folder 502)
      - 1944 (Box 158, Folder 503)
      - 1944 (Box 158, Folder 504)
      - 1944 (Box 158, Folder 505)
      - 1944 (Box 158, Folder 506)
      - 1945 (Box 158, Folder 507)
      - 1945 (Box 158, Folder 508)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 509)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 510)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 511)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 512)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 513)
      - 1946 (Box 158, Folder 514)
      - 1946 (Box 159, Folder 515)
      - 1946 (Box 159, Folder 516)
      - 1946 (Box 159, Folder 517)
      - 1947 (Box 159, Folder 518)
      - 1948 (Box 159, Folder 519)
      - 1949 (Box 159, Folder 520)
      - 1950 (Box 159, Folder 521)
      - 1950 (Box 159, Folder 522)
      - 1950 (Box 159, Folder 523)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 524)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 525)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 526)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 527)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 528)
      - 1951 (Box 159, Folder 529)
      - 1951 (Box 160, Folder 530)
      - 1951 (Box 160, Folder 531)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 532)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 533)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 534)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 535)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 536)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 537)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 538)
      - 1952 (Box 160, Folder 539)
      - 1953 (Box 160, Folder 540)
      - 1953 (Box 151, Folder 541)
      - 1953 (Box 161, Folder 542)
      - 1954 (Box 161, Folder 543)
      - 1954 (Box 161, Folder 544)
      - 1954 (Box 161, Folder 545)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 546)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 547)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 548)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 549)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 550)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 551)
      - 1955 (Box 161, Folder 552)
      - 1956 (Box 162, Folder 553)
      - 1957 (Box 162, Folder 554)
      - 1957 (Box 162, Folder 555)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 556)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 557)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 558)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 559)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 560)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 561)
      - 1958 (Box 162, Folder 562)
      - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 563)
      - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 564)
      - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 565)
      - 1959 (Box 153, Folder 566)
      - 1959 (Box 163, Folder 567)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 568)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 569)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 570)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 571)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 572)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 573)
      - 1960 (Box 163, Folder 574)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 575)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 576)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 577)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 578)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 579)
      - 1961 (Box 164, Folder 580)
      - 1962 (Box 164, Folder 581)
      - 1962 (Box 164, Folder 582)
      - 1962 (Box 165, Folder 583)
      - 1962 (Box 165, Folder 584)
      - 1962 (Box 165, Folder 585)
      - 1962 (Box 165, Folder 586)
      - 1963 (Box 165, Folder 587)
      - 1963 (Box 165, Folder 588)
      - 1963 (Box 165, Folder 589)
      - 1963 (Box 165, Folder 590)
      - 1964 (Box 165, Folder 591)
      - 1964 (Box 166, Folder 592)
      - 1964 (Box 166, Folder 593)
      - 1964 (Box 166, Folder 594)
      - 1965 (Box 166, Folder 595)
      - 1965 (Box 166, Folder 596)
      - 1966 (Box 166, Folder 597)
      - 1966 (Box 166, Folder 598)
      - 1967 (Box 166, Folder 599)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 166, Folder 600)
      - 1970 (Box 166, Folder 601)
      - n.d. (Box 166, Folder 602)
    - Mary Troth Haines
      - 1934-1947 (Box 167, Folder 603)
      - 1948-1953 (Box 167, Folder 604)
      - 1955-1968 (Box 167, Folder 605)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 167, Folder 606)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 167, Folder 607)
      - n.d. (Box 167, Folder 608)
    - Charles Huston Haines
      - 1932, 1946 (Box 167, Folder 609)
    - Mary Huston Haines
      - 1890-1921 (Box 167, Folder 610)
      - 1930-1946 (Box 167, Folder 611)
    - C. Haines
      - 1937 (Box 167, Folder 612)
    - Richard Haines
      - 1754-1767 (Box 167, Folder 613)
    - Bridget Kennedy
      - 1924-1932 (Box 167, Folder 614)
      - 1933 (Box 167, Folder 615)
      - 1934-1935 (Box 167, Folder 616)
      - n.d. (Box 167, Folder 617)
    - Benjamin Marshall
      - n.d. (Box 167, Folder 618)
    - Timothy Matlack
      - 1746-1771 (Box 167, Folder 619)
    - Isabelle Miller
      - 1960-1964 (Box 167, Folder 620)
    - Non Family Members
      - 1768-1861 (Box 167, Folder 621)
    - Other Family Members
      - incl. notes re DJH, 1779,1838,1919 (Box 167, Folder 622)
    - Thomas Broom Smith
      - 1856-1861 (Box 167, Folder 623)
    - Caspar Wistar, M.D., (1801-1867)
      - 1850-1857 (Box 167, Folder 624)
    - No Name
      - n.d. (Box 167, Folder 625)
  - C. Banking
    - Hannah Marshall Haines
      - Bank of Philadelphia: checks, 1825 (Box 168, Folder 626)
      - Farmers and Mechanics Bank: blank checks (Box 168, Folder 627)
      - Philadelphia Bank: check book, 1807-1815 (Box 168, Folder 628)
    - Reuben Haines III
      - Bank of Philadelphia: check book, 1808-1811 (Box 168, Folder 629)
      - Bank of Philadelphia: check book, 1815-1831 (Box 168, Folder 630)
      - Bank of Philadelphia: checks, 1826-1830 (Box 168, Folder 631)
    - Jane Bowne Haines I
      - Bank of Germantown: checks and bank book, 1831-1842 (Box 168, Folder 631a)
    - John Smith Haines II
      - Bank of Germantown: checks, 1846-1847 (Box 168, Folder 632)
      - Philadelphia Bank: bank book, 1849-1865 (Box 168, Folder 633)
      - Philadelphia Bank: checks, 1858-1861 (Box 168, Folder 634)
      - Philadelphia Bank: check stubs, 1849-1858 (Box 168, Folder 635)
    - Robert Bowne Haines I
      - Bank of Germantown: promissory note, 1858 (Box 168, Folder 636)
    - Margaret Vaux Wistar Haines
      - Provident Life and Trust Co.: including deposit book, statement, et al., 1916-1917 (Box 168, Folder 637)
    - Caspar Wistar Haines II
      - Bank of Richmond: check stub book, 1906-1907 (Box 169, Folder 638)
      - Commercial Trust Co.: bank statements, 1912-1914 (Box 169, Folder 639)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1919-1921 (Box 169, Folder 640)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1923 (Box 169, Folder 641)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1924 (Box 169, Folder 642)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1925 (Box 169, Folder 643)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1926 (Box 169, Folder 644)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1927 (Box 169, Folder 645)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1928 (Box 169, Folder 646)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1929 (Box 169, Folder 647)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1930 (Box 169, Folder 648)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1931 (Box 169, Folder 649)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1932, 1934 (Box 170, Folder 650)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1912-1929 (Box 170, Folder 651)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1913-1915 (Box 170, Folder 652)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1915-1927 (Box 170, Folder 653)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1917 (Box 170, Folder 654)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1919-1920 (Box 170, Folder 655)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1920-1922 (Box 170, Folder 656)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1922-1923 (Box 170, Folder 657)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1922-1923 (Box 171, Folder 658)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1924-1925 (Box 171, Folder 658)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1926-1927 (Box 171, Folder 659)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1929-1930 (Box 171, Folder 660)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1931-1932 (Box 171, Folder 661)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1932-1933 (Box 171, Folder 662)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1933-1935 (Box 171, Folder 663)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: check stub books, 1935 (Box 171, Folder 664)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: deposit slips & book, 1934-1935 (Box 171, Folder 665)
      - Germantown Trust Co.: statements, 1934-1935 (Box 171, Folder 666)
      - Girard Trust Co.: bank statements, 1934-1935 (Box 172, Folder 667)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1898-1899 (Box 172, Folder 668)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1907-1910 (Box 172, Folder 669)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1911 (Box 172, Folder 670)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1912 (Box 172, Folder 671)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1913 (Box 172, Folder 672)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1914 (Box 172, Folder 673)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1915 (Box 172, Folder 674)
      - Girard Trust Co.: cancelled checks, 1934 (Box 172, Folder 675)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1895-1899 (Box 172, Folder 676)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1898-1905 (Box 172, Folder 677)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1905-1909 (Box 172, Folder 678)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1909-1911 (Box 173, Folder 679)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1911-1912 (Box 173, Folder 680)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1912-1914 (Box 173, Folder 681)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1914-1927 (Box 173, Folder 682)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1917-1924 (Box 173, Folder 683)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1924-1927 (Box 173, Folder 684)
      - Girard Trust Co.: check stub books, 1930-1934 (Box 173, Folder 685)
      - Girard Trust Co.: miscellany including deposit slips, 1934-1936 (Box 173, Folder 686)
      - Metropolitan Bank of Virginia: check stub books, 1903-1905 (Box 173, Folder 687)
      - Pennsylvania Co.: bank statements, 1933-1935 (Box 173, Folder 688)
      - Saving Fund Society: deposit books, 1866-1930 (Box 173, Folder 689)
      - Trust Co. of North America, 1896-1920 (Box 173, Folder 690)
      - Union Trust Co., 1904-1919 (Box 174, Folder 691)
      - Other banks, 1877-1908 (Box 174, Folder 692)
      - Other banks, 1923-1941 (Box 174, Folder 693)
      - Miscellaneous deposit books, n.d. (Box 174, Folder 694)
    - Robert Bowne Haines II
      - Cheltenham National Bank: statements, 1943 (Box 174, Folder 695)